once I'm satisfied that I have added all
of the animations I require its then a
chance to review those animations and
make sure that everything's working
accordingly so I have animations to
every single flight but on the slide I'm
going to demonstrate how you can change
the way the animations appear and the
timings of the animations so at the
moment when I play the presentation and
I will do that demonstrate by just
playing slide one so far select slide 1
and start the slide sure nothing happens
until I actually click the most button
or press the spacebar so but when I
press the spacebar each of the elements
will appear but what I wanted to is I'd
like to be in a situation where I don't
have to press the spacebar or the actual
animations will appear automatically so
if I go back to the animations tab and
then select the animations pin you can
see that all of the animations that are
on that slate so there are four
animations and they all have a little
mouse icon next to them so if I just
actually hold down the control key and
select all four of those rather than
doing them individually I can then
change that from unclick to after
previous so what that means is that
rather than me having to click if I view
the slideshow again just from this slate
but don't have to click the information
will start appearing automatically as
well as that it may be a kiss that I
want the actual animations to not coming
as fast so I like them to slow down so
they take more time again what I can do
is I can select all four of the
animations and I can put a delay so what
I can do there is if I just added the
layer of 0.5 and then preview that as
you will see the animations will start
to appear a lot more slowly
and once I'm satisfied that the time in
delay is suitable I can then move on to
the next slide in addition to that you
can't actually change the order of your
animations so if I wanted the picture on
the right to appear before the pitch on
the left I can highlight the picture and
then move that up so if I preview that
again now the title would come in and
then the picture to the rate would come
in before the picture to the left and
then the text at the bottom so there are
a variety of things you could do so what
you can't do is you can have a play
around with that and try changing the
automation and the timings of your
animations